{
    "check_ins": [
        {
            "Week 1": {
                "current_question_index": 8,
                "Q1": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How is Martha's mood today?",
                        "options": [
                            "Agitated",
                            "Angry",
                            "Frustrated",
                            "Lost",
                            "Neutral",
                            "Happy"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Angry"
                },
                "Q2": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any of the following in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Increasing irritability",
                            "Wandering",
                            "Delusions"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Increasing irritability"
                },
                "Q3": {
                    "question": "How long did Martha sleep yesterday?",
                    "response": "5 hours"
                },
                "Q4": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How was Martha's sleep yesterday?",
                        "options": [
                            "Well rested",
                            "Woke up once",
                            "Woke up 2 or 3 times",
                            "Woke up 4 or more times",
                            "Disrupted"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Woke up 2 or 3 times"
                },
                "Q5": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any vomiting in the past week? (yes/no)",
                        "options": [
                            "yes",
                            "no"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "yes"
                },
                "Q6": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How many times in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Once only",
                            "2 to 3 times",
                            "4 to 5 times",
                            "More than 5 times"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "once only"
                },
                "Q7": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "For how long did the episode last?",
                        "options": [
                            "Less than 30 minutes",
                            "30 mins to an hour",
                            "1 to 4 hours",
                            "Full day"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "less than 30 minutes"
                },
                "Q8": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How did it impact Martha's daily activities?",
                        "options": [
                            "Difficulty eating and drinking",
                            "Difficulty walking",
                            "Fatigue",
                            "Severe dehydration"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "fatigue"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Week 2": {
                "current_question_index": 8,
                "Q1": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How is Martha's mood today?",
                        "options": [
                            "Agitated",
                            "Angry",
                            "Frustrated",
                            "Lost",
                            "Neutral",
                            "Happy"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "agitated"
                },
                "Q2": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any of the following in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Increasing irritability",
                            "Wandering",
                            "Delusions"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Wandering"
                },
                "Q3": {
                    "question": "How long did Martha sleep yesterday?",
                    "response": "upto 5 hours"
                },
                "Q4": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How was Martha's sleep yesterday?",
                        "options": [
                            "Well rested",
                            "Woke up once",
                            "Woke up 2 or 3 times",
                            "Woke up 4 or more times",
                            "Disrupted"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "disrupted"
                },
                "Q5": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any vomiting in the past week? (yes/no)",
                        "options": [
                            "yes",
                            "no"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "yes"
                },
                "Q6": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How many times in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Once only",
                            "2 to 3 times",
                            "4 to 5 times",
                            "More than 5 times"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "2 to 3 times"
                },
                "Q7": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "For how long did the episode last?",
                        "options": [
                            "Less than 30 minutes",
                            "30 mins to an hour",
                            "1 to 4 hours",
                            "Full day"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "30 mins to an hour"
                },
                "Q8": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How did it impact Martha's daily activities?",
                        "options": [
                            "Difficulty eating and drinking",
                            "Difficulty walking",
                            "Fatigue",
                            "Severe dehydration"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "fatigue"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Week 3": {
                "current_question_index": 7,
                "Q1": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How is Martha's mood today?",
                        "options": [
                            "Agitated",
                            "Angry",
                            "Frustrated",
                            "Lost",
                            "Neutral",
                            "Happy"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Lost"
                },
                "Q2": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any of the following in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Increasing irritability",
                            "Wandering",
                            "Delusions"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "wandering"
                },
                "Q3": {
                    "question": "How long did Martha sleep yesterday?",
                    "response": "upto 6 hours"
                },
                "Q4": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How was Martha's sleep yesterday?",
                        "options": [
                            "Well rested",
                            "Woke up once",
                            "Woke up 2 or 3 times",
                            "Woke up 4 or more times",
                            "Disrupted"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "woke up once"
                },
                "Q5": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any vomiting in the past week? (yes/no)",
                        "options": [
                            "yes",
                            "no"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "yes"
                },
                "Q6": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How many times in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Once only",
                            "2 to 3 times",
                            "4 to 5 times",
                            "More than 5 times"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Once only"
                },
                "Q7": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "For how long did the episode last?",
                        "options": [
                            "Less than 30 minutes",
                            "30 mins to an hour",
                            "1 to 4 hours",
                            "Full day"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Less than 30 minutes"
                }
            },
            "Week 4": {
                "current_question_index": 8,
                "Q1": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How is Martha's mood today?",
                        "options": [
                            "Agitated",
                            "Angry",
                            "Frustrated",
                            "Lost",
                            "Neutral",
                            "Happy"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Neutral"
                },
                "Q2": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any of the following in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Increasing irritability",
                            "Wandering",
                            "Delusions"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "none"
                },
                "Q3": {
                    "question": "How long did Martha sleep yesterday?",
                    "response": "Upto 8 hours"
                },
                "Q4": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How was Martha's sleep yesterday?",
                        "options": [
                            "Well rested",
                            "Woke up once",
                            "Woke up 2 or 3 times",
                            "Woke up 4 or more times",
                            "Disrupted"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Well rested"
                },
                "Q5": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any vomiting in the past week? (yes/no)",
                        "options": [
                            "yes",
                            "no"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "yes"
                },
                "Q6": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How many times in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Once only",
                            "2 to 3 times",
                            "4 to 5 times",
                            "More than 5 times"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Once only"
                },
                "Q7": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "For how long did the episode last?",
                        "options": [
                            "Less than 30 minutes",
                            "30 mins to an hour",
                            "1 to 4 hours",
                            "Full day"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Less than 30 minutes"
                },
                "Q8": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How did it impact Martha's daily activities?",
                        "options": [
                            "Difficulty eating and drinking",
                            "Difficulty walking",
                            "Fatigue",
                            "Severe dehydration"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Difficulty eating and drinking"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Week 5": {
                "current_question_index": 5,
                "Q1": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How is Martha's mood today?",
                        "options": [
                            "Agitated",
                            "Angry",
                            "Frustrated",
                            "Lost",
                            "Neutral",
                            "Happy"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Angry"
                },
                "Q2": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any of the following in the past week?",
                        "options": [
                            "Increasing irritability",
                            "Wandering",
                            "Delusions"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Wandering"
                },
                "Q3": {
                    "question": "How long did Martha sleep yesterday?",
                    "response": "Around 8 hours"
                },
                "Q4": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "How was Martha's sleep yesterday?",
                        "options": [
                            "Well rested",
                            "Woke up once",
                            "Woke up 2 or 3 times",
                            "Woke up 4 or more times",
                            "Disrupted"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "Well Rested"
                },
                "Q5": {
                    "question": {
                        "question": "Has Martha experienced any vomiting in the past week? (yes/no)",
                        "options": [
                            "yes",
                            "no"
                        ]
                    },
                    "response": "yes"
                }
            }
        }
    ]
}